一年2400次
一周44次
一天9次
每48分钟 就有一宗银行抢劫
这是全球银行抢劫之都
洛杉矶
贼巢
加迪纳 南洛杉矶 早上5：14
别别别兄弟！ 我们不是冲着你们来的！ 想都别想！
No, no, no, bro! We're not here for you! Don't even think about it!
别动 他妈的！
Don't you move, motherfucker!
手离武器远点儿 兄弟！ 你他妈的给我放松！
Hands away from the weapon, bro! Fucking relax!
我是3170 我们被围住了
3170. We're being held up.
穿甲子弹已经上膛了！
Armor piercing rounds are chambered in this firearm!
别逼我开火
Please don't be the asshole who forces me to use them.
脚从脚踏板上拿开
Take your foot off the gas,
按下开门键 然后从车里出来
press the unlock button, and step out of the vehicle,
否则我会强行把你拖出来！
or we will forcibly remove you!
快点 给我滚出来
Fucking do it! Now!
老实点 快点
Your choice! Go!
他妈的
What the fuck!
他妈的他是去摸他的枪了！
He fucking went for his gun.
他妈的他是把咖啡给洒了！
He spilled his fucking coffee.
见鬼！
Shit.
加迪纳 30秒
Gardena, 30 seconds out.
收到
Copy.
剩下30秒了 快点！
Thirty out. Hustle!
- 炸开它 - 准备好了
- Pop it. - Ready.
上！
Man on!
都他妈没时间了！
Out of fucking time.
准备好交火
Prepare to engage.
右边有敌人
Contact right!
100米 火力压制
Range 100. Suppressive fire.
左边有敌人！
Contact left!
1097出动 洛杉矶警察已到现场
Dispatch, 10-97. LAPD is on scene.
我们遭到了火力压制！
We are under heavy fire!
操你妈的！
Fuck!
他妈的
Motherfucker!
我来掩护你
Whoa, whoa. I got you. I got you.
快走 快走
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
他妈的刚刚是怎么回事？
What the fuck was that?
你看见他去碰枪了?
Did you see him go for his gun?
我不知道 我只看到博斯科把他崩了
I don't know. I just saw Bosco lit him up.
第二个路口左转进入隧道
Take the second left into the tunnel.
顺着机场 进入隧道
Hug the airport. Take the tunnel.
在多提右转
Go right on Doty.
多提右转
Right on Doty.
确保你们管好你们的枪
Make sure you take care of those weapons.
不希望有枪走火
I don't want any accidental discharges.
- 你看着他说这话干嘛？ - 雷
- What are you looking at him for? - Ray.
我不是在跟他说 我是跟你说
I'm not talking to him. I'm talking to you.
刚刚他妈的到底怎么回事？
What the fuck was that?
你他妈还搞砸什么了？
What else did you fuck up, huh?
你确定回来的时候没被跟踪吗？
You sure you were clean all the way home?
有尾巴吗？
Catch any tails?
马库斯打中的是哪？
Where did Marcus take those rounds?
股动脉 他死定了
Femoral artery. He's done.
我们知道这行有风险的
Well, we knew the risks.
突发状况 我们处理好了 没事儿了
Shit popped off. We handled it. That's it.
嘿 B
Hey, B.
回去那里
Get back over there.
看看是谁接手了 可能是洛杉矶治安局
See who responded. It was probably LASD.
他们比加迪纳警察职权大
They'll supersede Gardena,
但是如果是大案子 我们就有麻烦了
but if it's Major Crimes, we've got a problem.
都没问题了吧？没卫星追踪？
All clear? No GPS?
如果是老款仪器 我们就没问题
It's one of the old models, man. We good.
我们需要把祸给补上！
We've got to get this patched up.
需要干净利落！
We need this clean.
你还好吗？
You good?
我们现在成了警察杀手了
We're cop killers now.
看起来很疼啊
Well, that looks like it hurt.
不是吗？
No?
早上好 各位同事
Good morning, fellow officers.
嗯 -我猜他应该是坏人
I take it he's a bad guy.
你是指这个穿着黑色护甲
You mean the guy with the black body armor,
配有散弹枪和防毒面具的人吗？
shotgun, and gas mask?
你挺风趣啊 弄清楚他是谁了吗？
That's very funny. We know who he is yet?
昨晚很不顺？
Rough night?
是的 换个话题
Yes. Next subject?
你今天看着不那么性感啊
You're not looking so hot there, bubba.
我觉得他看着很棒啊
I think he looks amazing.
你还是少喝点儿“石榴汁”吧 周五尿检
You better start downing the POM juice, big man. We've got a piss test Friday.
是周四
Thursday.
你们他妈的摩门教的人是不是这个月都在喝青草汁儿？
What, like you Mormons have been drinking wheatgrass all fucking month?
别这样
Please.
这个你还有吗？ 我快饿死了
You got another one of those? I'm fucking starving.
还有俩个没沾上血的
Yeah, there's a couple that don't have blood.
好像就是那个粉色的 有巧克力粒儿的
I think it's one of the pinkies with the sprinkles.
- 这甜甜圈真是不错啊 - 哦 现在有什么数据？
- That's some real donut. - Okay, what's the tally?
老兄这些太可怕了
Those are horrendous, dude.
四个当场死了 六个送医院了
We've got four dead, six on the way to the hospital.
应该没有生命危险 操
- But they'll be all right. - Fuck.
来买早餐的时候被埋伏了
Ambushed them as they were coming to get breakfast.
他们的车被包围了
Surrounded the truck.
这个可怜鬼 只是想做好自己的工作
This poor fool right here was trying to do what he gets paid to do.
穿甲弹打穿了前玻璃 把他给崩出来了
AP rounds blasted through the windshield took him out.
他们抢走了卡车 加迪纳警察在霍索恩跟丢了
They took the truck, Gardena police lost them under Hawthorne Municipal.
他们对路线很熟
They knew the route.
选择加迪纳是因为它就在市机场旁边
Picked it because it was next to Municipal Airport,
因为飞行限制 所以他们知道不会有直升机追踪
knew the restricted air space meant no ghetto bird air support.
我们面对的劫匪不一般啊 伙计们
We're dealing with a different animal here, boys.
跟装甲卡车公司谈过了吗？ 丢了多少？
Talk to the armored car company? What was the haul?
他们是在去银行的路上 帮联邦银行取东西
They were en route to a bank pickup for a Fed drop.
但是车上是空的
But there was nothing in the truck.
空的？
Nothing in the truck?
他们他妈的偷了俩空的装甲卡车？
They stole a fucking empty armored truck?
是的
Yup.
为什么开枪？
Why the fireworks?
有个受害人说车警去摸枪了 那就是开打的原因
One of the vics said the messenger went for his gun. That's when it popped off.
真是个天才！
Genius.
好吧 那辆城市四驱 有什么线索？
Okay, the SUV, what have we got?
没什么有用的线索
That's a cold car.
引擎号撕掉了 车牌是偷的 没有指纹
VIN's been pried off. Plates are stolen. No prints on it.
他们还用漂白水给它炸了
They bleach-bombed it.
好吧 把它送到科学侦察科 罩起来 棉签全抹一遍 不放过任何细节
Right. Take it to SID. Tent that fucker. Swab it. Detail it.
操 这么早就让我和这个低能工厂周旋
Ah, fuck. I can't deal with this retard factory this early.
你们谁来吧
One of you guys handle it?
兄弟 只有你了
It's all you, bro.
谢了
Thank you.
好吧 有目击者吗？甜甜圈店员？
All right, witnesses, donut shop guy?
他看见他们了 他们直勾勾的对视了
He saw them, and they looked right at him,
但是不知道为什么没动他
but, for some reason, they left him alone.
好 收集所有的监控录像 车牌读取器 做个大数据筛查
Okay, pull all video surveillance and plate readers. Do a Palantir run.
跟交通部门联络
Talk to DOT, okay?
都收集好之后 我们在办公室碰头
Pull it all together, and meet me at the office.
把那该死的装甲车给我找回来
And find me that fucking truck.
老大尼克 警察血液中的原始黑帮份子
Big Nick, original gangsta cop in the flesh.
罗宾 '鲍勃'对吧？
Lobbin' Bob. Huh?
那个下流的网球局怎么样了？
How's that mean tennis game?
看看你 伙计！
Look at you, man.
你在哪买的？ 很不错的西服
Where'd you pick that up? Nice suit.
不是在你购物的地方 我给不起你这个钱
Well, not where you're shopping. I can't afford it.
我说 一个小小的镇警
I mean, how does a county sheriff
哪来的钱买这么漂亮的夹克？
pay for such a beautiful piece of men's fashion?
这坨狗屎？ 这是垃圾
You kidding me? This piece of shit? Nah, this is garbage.
看看你
Look at you.
这东西好比大奶子
This thing's tits!
你得什么屎勾当都干才能买得起它吧 是吧？
You must pull all kinds of ass sporting that, no?
好吧 我不能 我不想说了..
Nick, you know what? I can't. I can't.
大早上的 这么早我没法看你的马戏
It's too early in the morning for your fucking circus.
你刚刚把一个甜甜圈扔进案发现场里了
You just threw a donut in the hot zone.
-我没有吧！ -你有！
- No. I did not. - Yeah, you did.
我扔了？ 那样做太他妈错了
I did? That was fucking wrong.
是的 我不喜欢你 尼克 不喜欢你处理警察事务的方法...
It was. I don't like you, Nick, or how you handle police business...
嘿 你什么意思？
Hey, hey, hey. What's up with that?
我可喜欢你
I like you.
尽管你是个素食主义者
Aside from the fact that you're a vegetarian.
-是严格素食者！我是严格素食者
Vegan! I'm a vegan.
素食者是喝牛奶的 -哦 我为你感到遗憾
- Vegetarians, they eat milk... - Yeah, sorry to hear that.
你到底来干嘛的？
What are you doing here anyway, huh?
没有丢货币 这不是联邦案件
No legal tender was stolen. It isn't Federal.
暂时不是
Yet.
你定格是为了营造戏剧效果？
You're pausing for dramatic effect?
你简直就是个大坏警官！
You're such a big, bad lieutenant.
我知道 我知道
- I know. I know. - Yeah.
我能走了吗 老爸？ 我有点儿饿了
Can I go now, Dad? I'm kind of hungry.
加迪纳警察来了 控制了现场
So Gardena showed up, and they secured the scene,
然后这些小丑给接手了
and then these clowns took over.
他们是谁？洛杉矶治安局的？
Who are they, LASD?
是的 他们肯定是治安局的 看看这个小丑
Yeah, Sheriff's. They must be. Look at this clown right here.
他好像是头儿
He seemed to be in charge.
你对他有印象吗？
You recognize him?
他在南边玩儿过足球
He played football at South.
记得安德欧吗？警察干掉的菲律宾人
Remember Endo? Filipino dude the cops killed?
嗯
Yeah.
那就是崩了他的警察
That's the cop who blasted him.
他主管大案的
Runs Major Crimes.
要知己知彼 孩子们
Get to know your enemy, boys.
谁是这团伙的主使？
Who's running this crew?
可能有2-3人有能力做到
Probably two, three guys that can pull this off, max.
为什么要偷一辆空的装甲卡车？
Why steal an armored truck with nothing in it?
可能消息有误 白干了
Bad tip, they probably botched it.
那为什么没有把车扔掉？
Why didn't they dump it, then?
- 我查查废车场 - 所有的都查
- I'll check the salvage yards. - All of them.
他们怎么知道联邦机构要从赌场运东西？
And how'd they know about a transfer from the casino to the Fed,
特别是这次行程都没有通过日常的运输运作 怎么回事？
especially one that wasn't scheduled through the regular carrier? How?
肯定是有内奸 错不了
It was an inside job, bro. It had to be.
操 把止泻药给我
Oh, fuck. Give me the Pepto.
好吧 有内奸 那是哪个环节出错了
Okay, inside job, but where?
赌场？银行？ 还是他妈的甜甜圈店？哪个？
Right? Was it the casino, the bank, the Fed, the fucking donut shop? Where?
那梅利曼呢？
What about Merrimen?
-他是什么时候假释的？
When did he parole again?
-8个月前 - 8个月前？
- Eight months ago. - Eight months ago?
我们需要找到那辆该死的装甲车
We need to find that fucking truck.
威尔森那孩子你还跟着呢么？
Have we still got a tail on that Wilson kid?
-嗯
Yeah.
就是老和梅利曼一起的那个
The one who was hanging out with Merrimen?
在哪个酒吧工作来着？
What bar did he work in?
- 哈夫布劳 - 基奇的哈夫布劳
- Hofbrau. - Ziggy's Hofbrau.
我们去会会他
Let's pay him a visit.
有Wi-Fi吗？没有？ 我们最好看看他的录像带
...some Wi-Fi? No? We better check his videos.
- 谢谢 - 没事
- Thanks. - All right.
沃夫冈 要点什么？
Wolfgang, talk to me.
- 唐尼 我没钱了 - 没事
- Donnie, I'm tapped out. - No problem.
- 帮我记账上吧 好吗？
Put it on my tab, all right?
- 当然 兄弟 我帮你搞定 - 谢谢
- Of course, man, I got you. - Thank you.
晚安
Have a good night.
- 我们做这票吗？
Are we doing this?
- 是的 兄弟 好的兄弟
Yeah, man. All right, man.
- 为我们的钱和女人干杯
To money and women.
- 还没到手的
That we don't have.
你是怎么记住那么多人点的酒的？
How do you remember everybody's order like that?
- 我连我社保卡的最后4位都记不住
I can't remember the last four of my social.
- 不停的重复 兄弟
Lots of reps man.
我周边的环境是被我完全掌控的 他们根本不知道
I'm in complete control of my environment. People don't even know.
- 嘿 兄弟 该走了 - 好的
- Hey, man, time to go. - Okay.
收拾收拾
Wrap it up.
- 就一点点了
- Just a little bit. - Yeah, yeah.
- 嗯 基奇会杀了我 - 操 喝不完了
- Ziggy's going to kill me. - Shit, not going to finish.
-给你的礼物
A gift.
-小费呢？
How about a tip?
-上次给了
We got you last time.
-给了？
Oh, yeah, you got me last...
这不是规矩啊
That's not how it works.
是么？动物园野兽
Okay, really? Zoo animals.
需要换钱？
Need change?
是给你的 女士
That's for you, Fräulein.
谢了
Thanks.
老有好多警察来这吗？
Are there always so many cops in here?
我觉得他们不会选择来这儿
Last place I'd think they'd be.
嗯 这是他们的地盘 便宜的酒水
Yeah, this their spot. You know, cheap liquor.
嗯
Right.
这里什么样得坏人都有 是吧？
Yeah, there also is a lot of shady cats in here, huh?
嗯 是的 这里算是个中立地段吧 懂吗？
Yeah, it's kind of neutral grounds, you know?
就像 瑞克在卡萨布兰卡那样 那种
Rick's in Casablanca type shit.
你在这肯定听到了不少故事
You must've heard some stories in this place.
嗯 给他们两杯酒 来一碟牛排
You know, give him a couple of drinks, steak on his plate,
美丽的女人缠绕
some nice women around him,
他就会告诉你他最阴暗得秘密
he'll tell you his darkest secrets.
嘴松可以沉船
Loose lips sink ships.
说的不假啊
Ain't that the truth.
你呢？
Mmm, what about you?
在这可以钓到好多女人 对吧？
Pull a lot of pussy in here? Yeah?
-说说吧
Come on.
-我自己一个人挺好的
- I do well for myself. - Yeah.
我都愿意操你的
I'd fuck you.
开玩笑的
Kidding.
好吧
All right.
我要走了
I'm out.
再见兄弟
See you later, man.
是啊
Yeah.
很期待再见
Look forward to it.
-女士！ -操 你他妈的在干嘛...
- Fräulein. - Dude, what the fuck are you...
搞什么
What the fuck?
-还好吗 混混？
What's up, gangster?
-哦 桃子
Oh, Peaches.
哦 女士 你起来了
Oh, Fräulein, you're up.
坐下 你就坐这里
Sit down. You sit right there.
兄弟你走那么慢干嘛？
What you walking so slow for, nigga?
坐那 你就坐那
I want you to sit right there. That's you right there.
-看这儿 那是烟 -嗯
- Look here. There's cigarettes. - Yeah.
- 布若丘！
Borracho!
- 你们把我认错成别人了
I think y'all got me confused with somebody.
为什么我的裤子是湿的？
Why my pants wet?
兄弟们 如果你们和这位汤姆大叔在这
Come on, man, if you and your Uncle Tom over here
搞什么同性恋狗屎 我没意见
are into some homo shit, I'm good.
现在就直接杀了我吧
Y'all just kill me now.
你自己给尿了 傻孩儿
You pissed yourself, bubba.
有时候会的
It happens.
这里的女孩儿给你擦的 你没事的
I had one of the girls here clean you up, so you're good.
你抓错人了
But y'all got the wrong dude.
你把我认成别人了
You got me confused with someone.
-我现在就告诉你  我不是你要找的人
But I'm going to let you know now, I ain't the one.
-你怎么解释？
What'd you say?
说啥？
Dude something?
我们没认错你 别他妈的当个自作聪明的傻逼
No, we're not mistaking you for anybody. Don't be a fucking smartass.
因为盗车17岁被捕
Arrested at 17 for GTA.
作为成人案件被审判入罪
Tried and convicted as an adult.
我们清楚的知道你是谁
We know exactly who you are.
杀人未遂在郡监狱服刑
Did a stint at county for attempted manslaughter.
加利福尼亚历史上速度最快的超速罚单就是开给你的
Fastest speeding ticket in California history.
-很牛啊
That's nice.
-真他妈有才 你当时开的多快？
Fucking genius, man. How fast were you going?
每小时178公里
178.
速度恶魔啊!
Speed demon!
你和抓到你的警察是怎么说的？
What did you say to the cop who pulled you over?
用的什么理由？
What reason did you give him?
我说他们刚把新路面铺好
Told him they'd just paved the road.
- 我欣赏！- 有种
- I like him. - Ballsy.
我喜欢
Me gusta.
也许作为黑人你的丁丁有些小
You may have a little pecker for a black dude.
但是你他妈的还挺有风格的 兄弟
You may be a bed-wetter, but you've got some fucking style, buddy.
就这样吧 女士们 该走了
All right, girls, time to go.
拿着你们的鞋 你们的狗屎 走吧
Grab your shoes. Grab your shit. Let's go.
回去喂你们的宝宝们
Time to go home to your babies.
谢谢过来
- All right, thanks for stopping by. - Excuse me.
听听这个 热棒 你已经进去两次了
You check this out, hot rod. You're a two-striker.
我跟你说话的时候 你他妈看着我
You need to fucking look at me when I'm talking to you.
你就差一个错误就要面对每次洗澡都要被插屁股的人生了
You're one mistake away from getting sex in the ass every time you shower.
有的那些黑人和轮胎蹦一样粗
Some of them niggas got gas pumps.
对我个人来说 听着不是那么有趣
Now, personally, that shit don't sound like a lot of fun to me.
你怎么想的?感想如何？
What you think? How you feel about that?
照片里那个男人都不是我酒吧的常客
Look, the dude in that picture is not even a regular at my bar.
我看见过他几次 但我都不和他...
Like, I've seen him a few times, but, you know, I don't associate myself...
知道这个什么意思吗？
Do you know what this means?
我是一个小集团的成员
It means I am a member of a clique.
就像是个帮会
It's kind of like being in a gang.
就像是一个帮会 但是我们都有警徽
Sort of like a gang, only we have badges,
意思是你玩儿完了
which means you are done.
他没说谎
He ain't lying.
让我问问你这个
Let me ask you this.
你看看我们看起来像之前抓你的那些人吗？
Okay, do we look like the types who will arrest you?
给你戴上手铐 把你拉到警察局那些？
Put you in handcuffs, drag you down to the station?
- 我他妈的在问你一个问题！
I'm asking you a fucking question.
-一点儿不像
No. Not at all.
对了 很准确
Right, exactly.
我们就把你毙了 可以少写点儿报告
We just shoot you. It's less paperwork.
所以 说吧
So tell me,
你他妈的跟那帮人一起在干嘛呢？
what the fuck are you doing hanging out in that crew?
你就是个胆小鬼
You're a pussy.
他们都是大坏蛋
Those dudes are bad dudes.
大盗 有罪之人
Great thieves but straight convicts.
梅利曼和你这种人和啤酒在干嘛？
What's Merrimen doing drinking beers with the likes of you for?
谈工作?
Talk shop?
你们要抢酒吧？
You gonna hit the fucking Hofbrau?
把地方都拆了抢那5块10块的2000块钱？
Take the place down, score, like, what, two grand in ones and fives?
这就是正在进行的事情吗？我替你回答
Is that what's afoot? I'll answer that for you.
真他妈不是
No, it fucking isn't.
兄弟我不知道你说的是什么一班人
I don't know what crew you're speaking about, man.
-那个男的就是到我工作的酒吧喝酒
This dude just comes to my bar where I work...
-停！闭嘴
Stop. Shut up.
听着 兄弟 你们这样很奇怪 让我走...
Come on, man. This is some weird shit. Just...
听着 操蛋脸
You listen to me, fuckface.
我们才不在乎你
We don't give a shit about you.
你是梅利曼团伙的成员吗？
You in Merrimen's crew?
-体育场那票有你一份吗？
Huh? You hit the stadium?
你现在想说话了吗？
You talky-talky now?
-是的 求你了
Yes, please.
操!
Fuck!
我只是司机！
I'm just the driver!
他们不给我枪 我没参与帮会活动
They don't give me no gun. I don't do no gangster shit.
他们让我开车!所以我开车！
They asked me to drive, so that's what I do.
就那样！ 操！
That's it. Fuck!
为什么梅利曼要抢一辆空的装甲卡车？
Why did Merrimen hijack an empty armored car?
我不知道
I don't know, all right?
他们就怕我被抓了会乱讲 所以都瞒着我
They keep me in the dark for shit like this.
警察抓到我
If the cops come down on me,
我什么都不知道就不会乱说
I can't tell them shit if I don't know shit.
你可以给我连上
Now y'all can hook me up to a lie detector,
他妈的测谎仪 你有什么都可以
a fucking polygraph, whatever y'all got.
我所有知道的都告诉你了 你只能得到这些
I'm telling you what I know, and that's all you'll get.
求你了 操 放了我吧
Please, just let me the fuck go.
操 放了我吧
Fuck y'all, man. Let me go.
哇 我觉得你说的还挺能唬人的
Well, I thought that was relatively convincing, hmm?
好东西
Good stuff.
好吧 你什么时候见他的？
All right, when did you meet him?
-我能得到什么？
What do I get out of this?
-你能得到什么？嗯 一个是自由
What do you get out of this? Well, your freedom for one.
二
Two,
你并不是坏人
you're not the bad guys.
而我们是
We are.
2个月前他们来到酒吧
Couple months ago, they came through the bar,
我给他们倒了几杯酒
and I served them a few drinks.
-然后我们开始商议
We started talking.
-这是我的伙计博斯克
This is my boy, Bosco.
我同生共死的兄弟 我们一起服役的
My brother for life. We deployed together.
这孩子能开车
Hey, the kid can drive.
-好
Okay.
-唐尼 跟他讲讲Am系列的运输车
Donnie, tell him about the Trans Am Series.
我开过Am系列的运输车 就像他说的 开过4个月
Drove Trans Am Series, like he said, for about a season.
他们叫什么？
What were their names?
夏威夷人
Hawaiian dude,
他的死党博斯克是个白人
he had a homie, Bosco, white boy.
他之前服役过 之前在水利部工作
He was in the military, and he worked for DWP.
我跟他说我需要挣些外快
I told him I needed some extra money,
所以他给了我一个工作
so he gave me a job.
谁？梅利曼？
Who's that? Merrimen?
梅利曼
Merrimen.
雷 梅利曼
Ray Merrimen.
-这人怎么回事？
So what's up with this dude?
-马库斯的人
It's Marcus' boy.
之前在哈夫布劳一起上班
Worked with him over at the Hofbrau.
在维塞德监狱一起服过刑
Say he did some time with him at Wayside.
他之前不是军人么？
He was a Marine for a minute.
他说能开车 就没问题吧
Say the nigga can drive. He be cool.
好吧 我们去试探下他
All right, let's check him out.
真的很聪明的人
Real smart dude.
据我所知他刚出狱
He had just got out of prison from what I could tell.
准备好了吗 雷？
You ready to roll, Ray?
514号
514!
来吧给他戴上手铐
Come on, let's cuff them up.
很快再见 雷
See you soon, Ray.
你见不着了
No, you won't.
-你和他在哪会面的？
Where'd you meet him?
-在卡森 夏威夷人的家里
It was in Carson, at the Hawaiian dude's house.
唐尼 有什么好东西 兄弟
- Donnie, what's good, man? - What's up?
好吗？跟我来
- Come on, man. Follow me. - Yeah, yeah.
嘿
Hey.
- 嗯好吗？
Oh, shit. What's up?
- 唐尼 要啤酒吗？ - 好
- Donnie, beer? - Yeah, yeah.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
你在维赛德监狱待过？
So you spent some time at Wayside?
是的 待过一阵子
Yeah, a little bit.
每周五早上吃的是什么早餐？
What do they serve for breakfast on Fridays?
一块钱的那种煎饼
Silver dollar pancakes.
3个
Three of them.
你是哪儿的人？
Where you from?
霍索恩
Hawthorne.
你说你会开这个？
So you can drive, huh?
哦！我太会开了
Oh, I can drive.
开吧
Drive.
你也许该把安全带系上
You might want to put that seat belt on.
他喜欢我的一手车 所以一周之后我干了第一个活儿
He liked how I drove, so, a week later, I did my first gig.
我们把体育馆给抢了
We hit this rave at a stadium.
找到一个
Got one.
去掉有染料包的 其他的钱数对吗？
Minus the dye pack, is the count all good?
对的
The count is on.
兄弟 这里是很多的钱
That's a lot of money right there, bro.
我们收工吧
Why don't we just call it a day?
是吗？
Really?
你要三摞？
You want three in hot bills,
你的余生都在回头后悔？
you looking over your shoulder for the rest of your life,
还是想要30摞干净利落的？
or would you rather have 30 clean?
就是这个意思
I'm just saying.
还是在我们双赢的时候就收山吧
Let's just call it quits while we're ahead.
放起来
Put it away.
我们要买更高档的东西
We're trading up.
好吧 去他的 我们干吧
All right. Fuck it. Let's do it.
钱去哪了？
What happened to the cash?
我不知道
I don't know.
他们不告诉我
They don't tell me.
他们不怎么说话
They don't talk much.
有东西要藏的人从不会多说话
Yeah, people with things to hide never have much to say.
所以 我被捕了 还是我可以走了？
So am I under arrest, or can I leave?
还照旧生活
Nah, you just keep doing your thing.
我们会联系你
We'll be in touch.
嗯
Yeah?
马力 8点整到中心一号 别晚了
Horsepower, be at 1st and Central at 0800. Don't be late.
天！
Jesus Christ!
你吓我一跳 宝贝 你不能那样做
You scared the shit out of me, babe. Can't do that.
你现在在干嘛？
What are you doing right now?
删除最近的通话记录？
You erasing your recent calls?
我的电话里的？你什么意思？
My phone? What do you mean?
我根本不会使用这个鬼东西 你知道的
I don't know how to work this fucking thing. You know that.
“我根本不会使用这个鬼东西 你知道的”
"I don't know how to work this fucking thing. You know that."
别装了
Come on.
-宝贝 我们现在真的要为这个吵架吗？
Babe, we really have to go through this right now?
-你去哪了？
Where you been?
早上6点了 你去哪了？
It's 6:00 a.m. Where have you been?
在工作？
Been at work?
监视？抢劫毒贩？因为你全身都是脱衣舞娘味儿
Surveillance? Robbing drug dealers? Because you smell like a stripper.
我当然是在工作
Of course, I was at work.
那很奇怪 我收到了这条短信
It's funny 'cause I got this text.
什么那么性感啊？
What was so hot, then?
是工作短信吗？
Is that a work text?
你自己脑子进水了 发错给我了
You fucked up. You text me instead.
什么人啊？
Who does that?
只是和朋友吹吹牛的 不是你想的那样 我很抱歉
It's street theater, babe. It's not what it looks like.
我也是
I'm sorry.
-我们要去小姨家
We're going to go to Auntie's house
因为爸爸要把房子维修下
because Daddy's got to do a little work on the house.
我们还有别的事要做
And we have something else to do.
快点 -搞他妈什么啊
- Come on. - What the fuck?
- 嘿 你
Hey, yo.
- 这里对你们来说太吵了
It's gonna be too loud for you guys, okay?
-黛比 黛比 -把这个穿上
- Deb? Deb? - Will you put this on?
-爸爸一起来吗？ -黛比 你要干嘛？
- Is Daddy coming with us? - What are you doing, Deb?
你他妈的要干嘛？
What the fuck are you doing?
-对你们来说会很吵的 -老婆 老婆
- It will be too loud for you guys. - Wifey, wifey.
你认真的吗？你在干嘛？
Seriously, what are you doing?
-爸爸和我们一起来吗？
Is Daddy coming with us?
-不会 爸爸现在没有时间给我们
No, Daddy does not have enough time for us right now.
-你认真的吗？ 真是太棒了 太棒了
- Seriously... That's nice. That's nice. - Can you put this on here?
嘿 甜心 妈妈其实不是那个意思 知道了吗？
Hey, honey. Mommy didn't mean that, okay?
小甜心 过来 妈妈不是那个意思 知道吗？
Hey, sweetie, come here. Mommy didn't mean that, okay?
她不是那个意思 好吗？ 你还好吗 宝贝
She didn't mean that, okay? Sweetie, you okay?
好 好极了
Yeah, great. Great.
过来宝贝
Hey. Come here, honey.
我现在暂时可能做不到
I'm not going to be able to make it right now,
但是晚一点儿... 好吗
but I'm gonna come a little later, okay?
过来抱抱我
All right. Come here. Give me a hug.
-到时间要走了 -我靠
- Time to go right now. - Christ sake.
你慢点儿好不好
Will you slow it down a second?
让爸爸休息会儿 他累了
Give Daddy some rest. He's real tired.
对吧甜心
- Right, hon? - What...
黛比 黛比 你能缓一缓吗？
Deb. Deb. Deb, will you slow it down a second?
-我们走这边  好
- We're going to walk this way... - Deb.
注意台阶 -黛比 慢着
Okay, watch your step. Here we go.
黛比 慢着
Deb, can you slow it...
快点
Okay. Come on.
我们走喽 先把你妹妹放进车里
Let's go. We're going to put your sister in first.
-好了宝贝准备好了吗？
Here we go. Okay, baby, ready?
-甜心 会没事的 甜心 知道了吗？
Sweetie, it's going to be okay, sweetie. Okay?
我们走
Let's go.
把你的包放这儿 你需要让你妹妹坐这儿
Okay, put your bags in there. You wanna put your sister in the seat?
粉色的包去哪了？
Where's the pink bag?
操他妈的疯了吗？
Have you lost your fucking mind?
哦 在我女儿面前说这么粗俗的话
Oh, great language right in front of my daughter.
爸爸典范！
Great fathering!
-很好 很好 在我女儿面前说“操”
Nice. Nice. Dropping F-bombs in front of my daughters.
-说什么“我的孩子” “我的孩子”的 -你这爸爸当的真行
- "My kids," huh? "My kids?" - Great fathering!
我会找一个在我面前会硬的男人
Gonna find a guy whose cock actually gets hard for me.
黛比 黛比 停下来！
Deb, Deb, Deb. Stop!
请别这样
Please don't do this.
求你了
Please.
这有点儿难 你只是现在有点儿害怕 你不知道是怎么回事
This is a little hard. You're just scared right now, okay? You're confused.
尼克 让开 让开 尼克！
Out of the way, Nick. Get out of the way, Nick.
你他妈的给我滚开
Get the fuck out of here, you fucker!
你这个混蛋！
You motherfucker!
混蛋 你听见了吗？ 你这个混蛋！
You get back! You understand me, you motherfucker?
-离我们远点儿
- Stay away from us! - Nice. Nice.
-很好 很好
Good. Good.
没事 我没事
Okay. Mommy's okay.
晚些见
See you later.
太好了
Perfect.
早上好
Morning.
我把指纹在加利福尼亚侦察科鉴定过了
Ran the prints on CAL-ID.
和一个天使城的人对上了
Got a hit on our dead guy from Angel City.
-查下你的邮件 -好
- Check your e-mail. - All right.
叫马库斯 罗兹奥克兰人
Name's Marcus Rhodes, from Oakland.
枪支监管要抓他 起诉他
ATF was looking for him for gun charges.
还有证明之前你说对了
And more to the point that you were making before,
他之前在二十九棕榈村驻扎过 和梅利曼是同一时间
he was stationed at Twentynine Palms the same time Merrimen was there.
那很好 给我梅利曼的档案
This is good. Give me the book on Merrimen.
看你的右边
Look to your right.
知道那是什么吗？
You know what that is?
是银行的银行
It's the bank for banks.
是联邦银行在洛杉矶的分行
Los Angeles branch of the Federal Reserve.
这是唯一一间没有被打劫过的银行
It's the only bank that's never been robbed.
附近的所有街道都安装了声音和图像检测仪
All the surrounding streets are wired for sound and image.
只要你站在马路对面看着银行超过2分钟
Stand across the street and stare at the building for two minutes,
就会有保安礼貌的请你离开
you'll have security on your ass asking you politely to leave.
如果他们在那看见你第二次
If they see your face again,
全国所有的特勤部门人员都会来调查你
every Secret Service agent in the country is going to be looking for you.
这里无缝可钻
The place is case-proof.
有53次试图潜入的案例
There have been 53 break-in attempts.
没有一次能越过大堂
Not one has got past the lobby.
那就是为什么我们要抢劫这间
That's why we're going to rob it.
好 我们来看看
Okay, here we go.
拉古拉 尼格奥 是06年进去的
Laguna Niguel was in '06.
他被捕后被送到维克托维尔舒监狱
Got caught for that, get sent up to USP Victorville SHU
直到16年6月 给我下未破案的文档
until June of '16. Now give me the unsolved book.
你一进入到大堂
As soon as you enter the lobby,
电脑就会自动在全国罪案联网上核对你的资料
computers run you through every law enforcement database in the country.
如果你有未处理的停车罚单
If you've got outstanding parking tickets,
在你未接触到第一级的保安之前他们就都查清楚了
they're going to know about it before you get through the first level of security.
所有员工都有门禁卡
All the employees wear security swipe cards
这样他们就可以出入第一道人工检查关卡
that grant them access through the first set of man-traps.
出入是极其森严的
Access is severely restricted.
地下二层就是保险库楼层
Two stories below street level is the vault floor.
-顺便说一句
By the way,
这个坏人
uh, his crimey...
拉沃尔 -拉沃尔
- Levoux? - Levoux.
-他和梅利曼一起服过役吗？
He serve with Merrimen?
-不止 他们在长滩工艺学校的时候一起踢过足球
Not only that, but they played football in high school at Long Beach Poly.
-你他妈没跟我开玩笑吧 -没有
- You've got to be shitting me. - No.
-中央保安系统 就是联邦的中枢神经
Central Security, it's the nerve center for the Fed.
这里就是装甲车出入装卸钱箱的地方
This is where the armored cars come in, drop off the money tubs.
钱箱会直接交给联邦的员工
Money tubs are handed off to the Fed employees.
任何一个时间 在那里都储有5000到8000亿美元
At any one time, there's anywhere between 500 and 800 billion dollars in there,
每一寸都被摄像头和动作感应器所覆盖
every millimeter of it covered by cameras, sensors, and motion detectors.
-他们都擅长什么？
Yeah. What did they specialize in?
-这是我在二十九棕榈村人力资源找到的资料
I got this from the HR desk at Twentynine Palms.
近身突击队 两人都在中东真枪实战过
Close Quarter Battle Unit. Both saw combat in the Middle East.
拉沃尔是爆破专家 梅利曼是实战士兵
Levoux specializes in explosives, where Merrimen specializes in soldiering,
两人都是海军陆战特种兵快击手
both MARSOC fast Marines.
但是里面是有圈套的
But there's a hitch.
每一张钞票的序号都是记录在联邦的资料库里的
The serial number of every bill is recorded in the Fed's database.
如果任何一张不见了 不管是为什么不见
So, if a note goes missing,
他们都能知道是哪一张
they're going to know exactly which one it is.
钞票会被联网标记 只要那张钞票
They're going to flag it. If that bill comes up again,
在世界任何的一个角落再出现
whoever recirculates that cash, no matter where they are in the world,
他们就能找到持有钞票的人
that person can be tracked.
-那啄木鸟博斯克呢？
Okay. Bosco, the peckerwood?
-亨廷顿海滩男孩 也是海军陆战特种兵
He's a Huntington Beach kid, also MARSOC Marines.
他做过他们的联络员 前途光明
He did comms with them. He had a solid career.
但是他并没有和其他几人一起服役
But he didn't serve together with the other guys.
梅利曼在维克托维尔的时候 他是他们的代言人
He was the Wood Rep at Victorville when Merrimen was there.
他们就那样混到一起的
That's where they linked up.
唐尼做了一年半的士兵然后退伍了
Donnie was a Marine for a year and a half, then discharged.
我觉得
So, the way I see it,
这伙人就是这样走到了一起
that's the way all these niggas ended up working together.
我只看到这两个关联点 足球和服役
There's only two passports on the streets, sports and military.
每次联邦从银行接手存储金
Every time the Fed receives a deposit from a bank,
第一件事就是把钱都送去点钞室
first thing they do is send that money up to the count rooms.
钱被塞进点钞机
They run the notes through the counting machines.
两个目的
They're accomplishing two things here.
一 他们要再次检查数目是否准确
First, they're double-checking the accuracy of the bank's deposit.
如果多了少了
If the bank is off at all,
就会在账户上做加减法
they're going to credit or debit the account accordingly.
二 他们把新的钞票和旧的损坏了的钞票分开
Two, they're separating newer, fit currency from old unfit bills.
最重要的就是 他们会把废旧了的钞票序号从系统里删除
But most importantly, they're erasing the serial numbers
序号被删除
of the old bills from the Fed system.
那些钞票对政府和整个世界来说
Once those numbers are erased, to the Fed, to the rest of the world,
就已经不存在了
that money has ceased to exist.
我们来看看未侦破的案件
Wait, let's look at the unsolved cases.
04年的好莱坞博勒国家银行抢劫案
In '04, you have the Boller National Bank Hollywood job, okay?
他们是在下水道挖了通道
They tunneled through the sewer system.
很老练的 技术含量高 有人串通 没破案
Sophisticated, skill set, someone with access, unsolved.
05年 有弗尔特装甲车被劫案
Okay, in '05, you have the Fuerte armored car depot job.
用聚能药包炸开了保险库
Blew the depot vault with shaped charges.
光一百美元点钞室
In the $100 count room alone,
每天就有3亿美元被变成废纸
an average of $30 million is designated as unfit every day.
每天下午4点到5点之间
Between 4:00 p.m. and 5:00 p.m.,
所有费钱就会被运到粉碎机里
all the cash gets shot out to the shredder.
全都被销毁了
It's all destroyed.
3亿美元....几秒内就灰飞烟灭了
$30 million turned to dust in seconds.
然后联邦的合作垃圾公司
It's then picked up by the Fed's waste management company
会把粉末运到垃圾场扔掉
and brought out to the dump.
如果我们能在这些废钞被送进粉碎机
If we can get to those unfit bills
之前拿到它们 并全身而退...
before they go to the shredders and get out clean...
-我们就能拿到安全的3亿美元
You got $30 million nobody is looking for.
-答对了
Bingo.
06年 有拉古拉 尼格奥  跟之前一样
In '06, you have Laguna Niguel.
只是这次梅利曼不走运后车灯坏了
Same thing, only this time Merrimen gets unlucky with the tail-light.
服刑直到16年 在他服刑期间
Goes to prison till 2016. Now in that time, while he was in prison,
我们遇见过多少个纯熟 执行的极好的抢劫案呢？
how many highly sophisticated, well-executed heists do we have?
没有！但是你思路很对 继续说！
None, but you're on a roll. Keep going.
甜甜圈的收银员 目击了整个过程
The counter guy at the donut shop? Witness to the whole thing.
他们为什么要放过他？
They left him. Why?
因为他们只打军装 不会伤害无武装的平民
Because they shoot uniforms, not unarmed civilians.
那就是他们以前训练出来的结果
Exactly what they were trained to do.
普通黑社会小混混？ 他们可不是
Gangbangers, these are not.
这些就是我们要找的人
Okay, these are our guys.
我们把他们给搞定了 所有案子就都破了
We nail these guys, we solve all these cases.
就是这个团伙
This is the crew.
你还没有告诉我们要怎么通过安保
You still haven't told us how you can get past that security.
我们不从这里进去
We're not going in this way.
我们从那儿进去
We're going in that way.
-那女士呢？
What's going on with Fräulein?
-我们随时可以逮他
We can move on him anytime we want.
-我只给最低工资 -好
- I pay minimum wage. - Okay.
-每单外卖佣金3美元 小费你我平分
Plus $3 for delivery. And you split the tip with me.
周三11点开工
You start Wednesday, 11:00.
谢谢你
Thank you.
-我不喜欢那的食物 但是我还可以去
I don't really like the food there, but I'm down to go,
但是你要埋单 -我不给钱
- but you've got to pay this time. - I'm not paying it.
啥
What?
-他妈每次都是我请 -啥？
- I pay every fucking time. - What?
-别那么吝啬了
Get off your wallet, buddy.
-我今天忘带钱包了 孩子们 对不起了
No, I forgot my wallet today, boys. I'm sorry.
-又忘带？ -又？
- Again? - Yeah, again.
-你是鳄鱼臂
Got an alligator arm.
-我用5美元赌黑杰克 挣了160
I sat down at blackjack with $5, and I made $160.
尼古拉斯 奥 布莱恩？
Nicholas O'Brien?
干嘛？
Yeah?
我建议你收下这个
I suggest you take these.
你被法院传唤了
You're being served.
-你开玩笑吗？
You kidding me?
-我恐怕不是
I'm afraid not.
什么事？
What's going on?
兄弟 你还好吗？
You all right, bro?
额 我猜我要离婚了
Yeah, I guess I'm getting divorced.
他说 “离婚”？
He say "divorced"?
嗯
Yo.
欢迎加入俱乐部
Welcome to the fucking club.
去处理的你事情吧 大佬
Now, go handle your business, big man.
这是近距离细节
There's a closer view.
4天前这里有个停电盲点
There was a rolling blackout in this quadrant four days ago.
对 上几个月他们经历了好多次
Yeah, they've been happening a lot over the last few months.
嗯
Okay.
他们对外说他们有备用电 其实根本没有
They say they have full backup power, but actually they don't.
-他们进入节电模式 -优先供电
- They go into brown-out. - Yeah, prioritize the grid.
肯定是优先给保险库 所以保险库很完好
Priority, of course, is the vault. So everything in there stays intact.
但是外围的所有东西 比如走廊的摄像头
But anything that is peripheral, like cameras in the hallway,
点钞房里的碎纸机都没电了
shredders in the count rooms, everything else cuts out.
但是要预测下一次停电的时间简直是天方夜谭
To time it during another rolling blackout is going to be fucking impossible.
-所以你想自己制造？ -我们行吗？
- So you want to simulate it? - Can we?
潜入 让他们有两分钟进入节电模式
Break in, have them go brown for about two minutes.
-我们假设可以 但我需要更多的数据才能确定
I'd say yes, but I'd like to have data to be sure.
-很好
Great.
我们一旦进入了点钞室 只有摄像头要担心了
Once we breach the count room, only thing left is the cameras.
他们是自带电源的
They run on their own power supply,
他们不会被节电模式所影响
so they're unaffected by the brown-out.
解决办法就是用电磁脉冲波
The solve here is we run an EMP burst.
应该可以废掉9米之内的监视器和动作感应器
Should take out the cameras and motion for about 30 feet.
这些信息是从哪里得来的？
Where you get all this information from?
你根本不必知道
You don't have to worry about that.
你只需要知道信息很可靠就行了
Just trust me when I say it's solid.
勾线做的怎么样了？
How we doing with the Telecal hook?
还需要几天 应该不是问题
Couple days. Shouldn't be a problem.
你需要多少人支援？
How many handlers do you need?
我现在在B大门
Uh, gate B right now.
大摇大摆的走向联邦储蓄
Strolling right into the Federal Reserve.
武装人员离开B卸货口
Force leaving loading dock B.
身份证？
ID?
签字
Sign in, please.
必须随身携带这个 用第二区域的电梯
Keep this on you at all times.
到2层的用餐区
Second bay of elevators. Cafeteria's level 2.
让他进去 他可以通过
Buzz him in. He's good.
闻起来很棒
Smells good.
他没事 让他进去
He's good. Let him in.
-莎伦？ -是我
- Sharon? - Mmm-hmm. That's me.
-你好 -你今天好吗？
- How you all doing? - Good. How you are doing today?
-他挺俏的 -谢谢
- He's fine. - Thank you.
-她可钓不到你
She ain't getting none.
-闭嘴！别这样
Shut up. Really?
-祝你一天愉快 -我可不插嘴了
Y'all have a good day. I'm gonna stay out of it.
-肯定会愉快了
- We will now. - You have a wonderful day.
-午餐 甜点 午餐 甜点...
Lunch. Dessert. Lunch. Dessert.
再见 甜心
Bye, sunshine.
看他表演
There he goes.
我的天
My gosh.
他来了
- Oh, he's here. - Okay.
-天哪 你看起来太美了 -谢谢
Damn, girl looking fine.
-你看起来很棒
Thank you. You look amazing.
-你好吗？
How are you?
-你看着真棒 -谢谢
- Looking good. - Thank you.
-这是我妈妈 这是奥兰多
- This is my mom. This is Rolando. - Hi.
-很高兴见到你
- Nice to meet you. Rolando. - Hi, I'm Malia. Nice to meet you.
-我现在知道你这么美是遗传谁了
- I see where you get your looks from. - Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
-我来拿着这个 -好
- Can I take that? - Oh, yeah, sure.
-奥兰多 这是我爸爸
Um, Rolando, this is my dad.
你好吗 拉沃尔先生
What's up, Mr. Levoux? Nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你
Let me holler at him for a second.
我想跟他单独说两句话
Let me talk to you, bruh.
好的让我跟您说 别担心 他们只是说说话
Honey, don't worry about it. Okay? They're just gonna talk.
情况是这样的
So here's what's up.
在过去的16年里
For the past 16 years,
我女儿的安全和保护都是我的责任
my daughter's safety and protection has been my responsibility
只是我一个人的责任
and my responsibility only.
现在 她人生中的第一次 我要把这责任交给你
Now, for the first time in her life, I see I've got to hand you that responsibility.
别搞砸了
Don't fuck up,
不然在你的余生 你妈要哭着
or your mama will weep as she has
把你在轮椅上推来推去
to wheel your ass around every day the rest of your life.
我练习过了 因为我想用最友善的方式告诉你
Now I worked on this, because I want to say this to you as nice as possible.
-你明白吗？
Do you understand?
是的 先生
Yeah. Yes, sir.
没事 没事
It's all right. It's all right.
听着
Listen. Listen.
他只是想说很高兴见到你
All he's trying to say is, it's wonderful to meet you,
他想祝你有一个美好的夜晚
and he wants you to have a beautiful evening.
今晚11点半见？
I'll see you at 11:30.
-知道了
Yeah. Yeah.
11点半 11点半 - 选的不错
- 11:30. Yeah. 11:30. - Good choice.
我想他搞清楚情况了 兄弟
I think he got the picture, bro.
啤酒和清酒 走着！
Beers and sake, let's go.
- 喝酒 - 搞什么的
- Have wine. - What the fuck?
嘿
Hey.
兄弟
Buddy.
-唐尼 对吗？
Donnie, right?
-怎么了？
- Yeah. - Yeah.
-我那天在健身房见到你了
Yeah, spotted you at the gym the other day, yeah?
-嗯 你怎么样
Yeah, man. How you doing?
兄弟们 好吗？
What's up, fellows?
你之前在长滩工艺学校踢球？
You play football at Long Beach Poly?
你看着眼熟
You look familiar.
不是 我不是这里的人
No, I'm not from around here.
你来这干什么？上班吗？
What are you doing here? You work around here?
我来这享受晚餐
Enjoying my dinner, man.
真的？
- Really? - Yeah.
这的东西多难吃啊
Food here sucks.
我们都是来这撩妹的
Yeah. Yeah, we come here for the ass.
那健身房见吧
So I'll see ya at the gym, man.
好的
Yeah. Definitely.
祝你今晚愉快
Have a good night.
你是55号吧 我记得你的号码
Number 55, right? That's how I remember you.
你跟我一样是55号 对吧？
We wore the same number, 55, right?
我去过南托伦斯
I went to South Torrance.
我们跟你们打过几次比赛
Yeah, we played you guys a couple of times.
你队里有不少萨摩亚肥佬
You and all those fat-ass Samoans.
这帮肥佬体格大 还很懒
Yeah, they were big, but, man, lazy motherfuckers.
我们把你们虐成狗
Probably all that Spam.
我带队时就虐你们
Yeah, we fucking crushed you guys.
你带队也是挨虐
Crushed you guys when I was there. Crushed you guys when you were there.
你们一直被我们虐
Still crushing you guys.
我哥们都在这呢
We've got family here, bro.
你要是能自己出去就最好不过了
Don't really appreciate you popping off.
好吧 别激动 没必要这样
All right. All right, man. No need to get all agro.
我刚才说话伤人吗？
Was I being rude? Was I being rude?
什么？走吧
- What? - Let's go order, bro.
兄弟 听我说
Hey, look, man, listen.
你这几个哥们真不错 没人想惹麻烦 我们这就走
You've got a beautiful family. Everything's all good. Excuse us.
走喽
Kampai.
健身房见了 唐尼
See you at the gym, Donnie.
女士们 祝你们今夜玩得开心
Have a good night, ladies.
你是警察吗？
You a cop?
不是 你是吗？
No. Are you?
下车
Get out of the car.
那边走
Go!
你把窃听器藏哪了？
- Where's the wire? - Come on, man.
- 我他妈身上没有窃听器
I'm not wearing a fucking wire, man.
我说我他妈身上没有窃听器
Man, I'm not wearing no fucking wire.
起来
Get up.
他怎么认识你的？
How does he know you?
别跟我说你俩是他妈在体育馆认识的
Don't tell me it's from the fucking gym.
我跟他不熟
Look, I don't know him.
- 崩了他吧
Smoke this punk.
说实话 你这混账
Talk, motherfucker.
我不是警察
I'm not no cop, all right?
是他过来跟我说话的 他认识你
Now he came to me. He know you.
他认得你们所有人 我什么也没跟他说过
He know all of you. But I ain't tell him shit.
他吓唬我 然后我就再也没见过他
He was sweating me. I ain't seen him since.
我以为他不会来找我们了呢
I thought he'd leave us alone.
他们知道多少？
So how much do they know?
他们什么都不知道
Nothing.
我什么都没说
I ain't tell them shit.
我也什么都不知道
I don't know nothing anyway.
你知道我是值得信任的
And you know I'm the last person that would fuck this up.
如果任务取消 我能理解
Now, if we've got to call it off, I get it.
但是我什么也没跟他说
But I know I ain't tell them shit.
周五 会告诉你全部计划
Friday. Make sure he knows it's on.
真不错
So good.
是真的 真的
It's true, though. It's true.
好的
Okay.
最近还好吗 尼克？
How you doing, Nick?
我是尼克 - 你好
- I'm Nick. - Hello.
你好啊
- How are you? - Good.
嘿 晚饭..
What's for...
- 晚饭吃什么？ - 尼克 你真是一股酒味
- What's for dinner? - You smell like alcohol, Nick.
放松
Relax.
我来之前已吃过了
I already ate.
给我拿根笔 老兄
Give me a pen, stud.
- 尼克 我本想给你打电话的
Nick, I was gonna call you.
我原想请你吃饭
I was gonna take you to dinner next week.
- 赶紧给我他妈拿根笔
Just give me a fucking pen.
谢了 拉德
Thanks, Rudd.
我还是去... - 给我坐下
- I'm gonna hit the... - No, you're not.
酒好喝吗？
How's the wine?
好喝吗？
Good?
这酒挺他妈好喝啊
That's pretty fucking good.
我想我就...
So I imagine I just, uh...
随便找个地方签名就好了
What, just sign anywhere, yeah?
是吗？
Okay.
假设你敢碰我的女儿
And I imagine it's assumed that if you were ever
敢跟他们说话
to touch one of my girls or, say, talk to them
哪怕只是看他们一眼...
or, you know, even look at them,
我就会...你懂的吧？
I go boom-boom. You know what I'm saying?
你最好懂
But, I mean, that's self-evident, right?
我想我刚才说的就不用写进合约里了吧?
There's no need to put that in the contract, is there?
- 尼克 - 我可不这么想
- No, I didn't think so. - Nick...
请你现在离开好吗 尼克？
Can you please go, Nick?
都签完了吧 尼克？ - 当然
- That's enough, Nick. - Sure.
起来
Come on.
起来 跟我拥抱一下
Come here. Give me a hug.
这样我们就不用费钱做心理咨询了
Come on. We'll save a fortune in therapy.
跟我拥抱一下啊
Come on. Give me a hug.
这才对嘛
There you go, huh, hoss?
- 什么事你都搞成种场面吗？
You've just always got to make a spectacle out of everything.
这才对嘛
There you go.
差不多吧
Yeah, pretty much.
好了 尼克 我想你该走了
All right, Nick. I think it's time to go.
好了 尼克 走吧
Come on, Nick, let's go.
报警啊你们
Call the fucking cops. That's what I'm saying.
- 我很抱歉 但你真的得走了
- Call the fucking cops. - I'm sorry, but it's time for you to go.
- 快报警
Call the cops.
很抱歉 - 你别他妈碰我
- I'm sorry... - Don't fucking touch me.
- 抱歉 - 别碰我
- I'm sorry. - Do not fucking touch me.
- 行了 尼克 - 请你快走吧
- Come on, Nick. - Just, please go.
你们慢慢来
Take your time.
你经历了什么？
What happened to you?
博拉科 你看我这身怎么样？
Borracho, what do you think?
你他妈之前说那堆话是什么意思？
What the fuck was that?
你在健身房看到我了？
You spotted me at the gym?
- 别激动 好吧
Tranquillo. All right?
坐下
Sit down.
这衣服我要了
I'll take it, Freddy.
我跟他单独聊一会儿 好吧？
Just give us a minute, okay?
他们不会杀了你的
Look, they're not going to off you with this much heat, okay?
他们什么时候行动？
When's this happening?
-周五
Friday.
在哪？
Where?
我不知道 我只知道他们周五行动
I don't know yet. All I can tell you is Friday.
感谢上帝今天已是星期五了
TGIF, huh?
你会保护我的 对吗？
You're protecting me on this.
小姑娘
Fräulein,
我们会保护好你的 兄弟
we got your back, bro.
不用担心
Don't worry about a thing.
操
Fuck.
你们最好穿防弹衣
Better wear your vest.
我们会的
We're in.
Z?
皮科里维拉银行 在蒙特贝拉中心
Pico Rivera Savings, Montebello Town Center.
- 收到 8点见
Copy that, boss. See you at 0800.
- 把信息告知全组成员
Tell the crew.
我按你说的做了
I did what you told me to.
星期五 干得漂亮
There you go. Good job there.
麦坎娜
McKenna!
嘿 宝贝
Hey, sweetie. Hey, sweetie.
你最近怎么样 还好吗？
How are you? Good?
你在这干嘛呢？
What are you doing?
我正要去上班 路过此地
Well, you know, I was on my way to work
所以就想来看看我的小猴子
and thought I'd come by and say hello to my little monkey.
行不？
Is that okay?
在学校怎么样 还好？
How's everything at school? Okay?
- 是啊 还好
- Yes, it's good. - Yeah?
你阿姨家怎么样
And what about Auntie's house?
你妈妈和卡西还好吧？
Mommy and Cassady, are they good?
你的玩具熊呢 还好嘛
What about the honey-bear? Honey-bear good?
你想我了吗？
Yeah? You miss me?
好啦 小宝贝 回去上课吧
All right, Pookie, better get back to class.
我什么时候还能见到你？
When am I going to see you again?
快了 宝贝 就快了
Soon, sweetheart. I'm gonna see you soon.
我想回家
I want to come home.
我也想
Me, too.
好了 你快回去上课吧
All right, you better get back to class, okay?
再见啦
But I'm gonna see you later.
你保证会再来看我？
Promise?
我保证
I promise.
来 击拳为证
Come on.
休息结束了 孩子们都回来吧
Recess is over. Come on, kids. Come line up.
回去吧 宝贝
Go on, Pookie.
老爹 再见
Bye, Daddy.
快点 麦坎娜
Come on, McKenna.
快点 亲爱的
Come on, honey.
带好武器
Jock up.
你好啊 老哥
Tac up, brother.
不抢联邦储备局了？
No Fed?
计划有变
Change of plans.
听好
Pay attention.
除非必须开枪打人 否则你的手指一定别放在扳机上
Always keep your finger off the trigger until you're going to shoot somebody.
如果必须开枪 先得打开保险
If and when that happens, safety selector switch.
一下是半自动 两下是全自动开火
One for semi, two for full auto.
准备好弹夹
Mag release.
没子弹就换弹夹
Out with the old, in with the new.
检查弹夹是否装好
Tug it. Make sure it's in there good.
然后给枪上膛 准备下一轮射击
Slap the bolt home, you're ready for round two.
不开枪的时候 枪口一定对准地面
Other than that, keep this thing pointed at the fucking floor.
懂了吗？
- You understand? - Got it.
穿戴好装备
Go put your shit on.
博拉科 给我来个弹夹 - 好的
- Magazine, Borracho? - Yeah.
准备好了？  - 是的
- We good? - We good.
嫌疑犯已到既定位置
Suspects arriving on location.
我们没有证据给地区检察官看 他们还没展开犯罪行动
We've got nothing for the DA. They haven't committed a crime yet.
他们抢完银行我们就动手抓人
They clear the bank, we take them down.
各单位就位 - 收到
- Stand by. - Roger that.
大白天的
Broad fucking daylight.
他们全副武装
They're packing big.
靠 看看这群混账东西
Ooh, shit. Look at these motherfuckers.
全都趴下 全都趴下
Get down on the ground! Get down on the ground!
动全都趴下
Down on the ground! Get down on the fucking ground!
都别动
Freeze!
都别动 呆在那
Freeze! Don't move! Stay right there!
都别动
Freeze!
你们两个 去那边
- You two! Move! Get over there! - Get over here!
速度快点
Hurry up!
滚出来 速度快点
Get out here, now!
快点
Move there now! Go! Go! Go!
别动 待在那别动
Move back! Stay right there! Now!
手都放在地上
Eyes to the floor!
听好
Listen up!
大家都听好了
Everybody pay the fuck attention!
手放在地上
Eyes to the ground!
我只说一次
'Cause I'm only going to say this once!
如果你们合作 听从指挥
If you cooperate, if you follow directions,
我们就绝不会伤害你们 我们只图财 不想杀人
you will not be hurt. We are here for money, not for you.
所有人都出来沿着柜台趴好
I want everybody lined up on the counter. Let's go!
快点
Move down!
Move down! Let's go!
速度快点 柜台后面的也都出来 快
Everybody behind the counter, come out front! Let's go!
把头低下 别乱看也别乱说话
Keep your eyes down and your mouths shut.
听我命令
On my command,
把兜里的手机都给我拿出来
reach inside your pockets, remove your cell phones,
然后举起手来
and put your hands in the air.
所有人 向前两步
Everybody take two steps forward.
都跪下
Now go down on your knees.
手机都扔进来
All right! Cell phones right in here.
都老实点
On me.
快点 手机都扔进盒子里
Let's go. Put them in the box.
把他们手捆上
Tie them up.
快快快
Go! Go! Go!
谁也别逞英雄
There will be no heroics today.
老实地呆着
You guys go ahead and get comfortable.
你们得在这呆一阵子了
We're going to be here for a while.
有想去上厕所的
Anybody need to use the bathroom?
往裤裆里尿吧
Take a piss on yourself.
你 起来
You. Get up.
别动
Stop.
坐下
Sit down.
我需要你冷静下来
All right, I need you to calm down right now.
嘿 跟你说话呢 看着我
Hey! Look at me.
深呼吸
Take a deep breath.
好
Good.
我知道你已经按过无声警报器了
I know you already triggered the silent alarms.
所以我需要你拿起电话
So I need you to pick up the phone,
拨打911后 按我说的跟警察说...
dial 911 dispatch, and explain the following.
你得把我的话写下来
Go ahead and write this down.
这里发生211案件 劫匪有人质
There's a 211 in progress, and we have hostages.
在一小时内 他们得给我送来一千万美金
Within one hour, they need to deliver $10 million
必须都是未标记的小面额钞票
in unmarked small denomination bills to this bank
要用警局直升机运来 加满油
inside a department helicopter loaded with fuel.
跟他们说 不满足我们的要求 每隔一小时 我们就杀死一名人质
Tell them we plan on killing one hostage every hour until our demands are met.
不允许警察接近银行
No cops are to approach the bank.
如果安排谈判专家来 他敢张嘴
And if a negotiator even tries to contact us,
我就马上杀死一名人质
we will automatically kill another hostage.
听懂了吗？你都记下来了吗？
Is that clear? You got it all?
打电话吧
Go ahead and pick up the phone.
有外勤警队暂时没任务吗？
Any available units, we have a bank 211 in progress...
他妈的
Shit.
在皮科里维拉银行发生抢劫案 地址是蒙特贝拉
...at the Pico Rivera Savings in Montebello
威尔考克斯路和亚特兰大路岔路口 2891号
at 2891 Wilcox and Atlantic.
嫌犯都有武器 - 该死 这帮混蛋
- Suspects are armed... - What the fuck?
劫持人质 拒绝谈判
...and have taken hostages and are refusing a negotiator.
他们在干什么？这不是他们的以往手法啊
What the fuck is going on? That's not their MO.
向总部汇报 我们就在案发地点监视
Call in, tell them we're on scene, have suspects under surveillance,
让他们都撤退
and to back the fuck off.
我们是洛杉矶县治安官 我们正监视嫌犯
This is LASD, we have surveillance on the bank. Stand down.
请下令所有警队小组撤退 我重复 全部撤退
I repeat, have all units stand down.
靠 我都听到警笛声了
It's bullshit. I can hear them already.
你们他妈的在干什么？
What the fuck are they doing?
停车
Stop!
出来
Get out!
你们他妈的在干什么？
What the fuck are you guys doing, huh?
混蛋
Asshole!
你们他妈的在干什么？
What the fuck are you doing? What's going on?
你监视着嫌犯 还让他们控制了银行和人质？
You were running surveillance, and you let this shit go down?
这是我们的案子 我们监视他们好几个星期了
It's our fucking case. We've been surveilling these guys for weeks.
监视他们
That's what surveillance is!
就是想在他们犯罪的时候抓捕他们
They commit a crime, and then we stop them.
走 去金库
Go. Go to the vault.
把金库打开
Open it.
我们走 来
Let's go. Come.
在这坐下
Sit. Sit down.
我开免提
I'm going to put this on speaker phone.
你来接电话 但不能说名字
You're going to answer, but don't use any names.
懂吗？
You understand?
你好
Hello?
你好 我们是洛杉矶警察
Hello, this is the Los Angeles Police Department.
跟我通话的人是谁？
Who am I speaking with?
我是这的分行经理
This is the branch manager.
我需要跟匪徒头领说话
Sir, I need to speak with the person in charge.
我听着呢
You are.
好 我先自我介绍下 我叫...
Okay, good. Well, let me introduce myself. I'm Officer Parada...
老子不在乎你是谁 我们要求的东西 你们都准备好了吗？
I don't give a fuck who you are. Are our demands being met?
现在跟我说话的是谁？
Who am I talking with now?
- 回答问题
Answer the question.
- 我们正在准备
It's being worked on as we speak.
但请你理解一下...
But you need to understand...
你害死了一名人质
You just killed a hostage.
该死的
God damn it!
起来 - 不要啊
- Get up. Get up! - No! No! No!
起来
Come on, move!
我什么也没做 求求你 你要干什么
I didn't do anything. Please. What are you doing?
求求你 不要杀我
- Come on. - No! No! No!
该死
Fuck!
- 妈的 - 都在你们掌控下？
- You were on it, huh? - Shit!
你这蠢货
You're so full of shit, O'Brien...
你知道他们的条件
You heard the demands, you stupid motherfucker!
还派谈判专家联系他们？
- Yeah. - You put a negotiator on? Christ!
- 去你妈的 - 你骂我？
- Fuck you! - Fuck me?
- 骂的就是你
Yeah, fuck you!
- 你自己犯傻
Fucking nice haircut, you fucking idiot.
你他妈还推我？
Who are you fucking pushing now?
你他妈开玩笑呢？
Are you fucking kidding?
- 立即汇报总部 - 你这混蛋
- Get SWAT rolling right now! - You fucking pussy.
你这傻逼还生气了？
Fucking Lobbin' Bob is angry!
- 好了 老大 我们走 - 他妈的
- All right, boss, let's go. Let's go. - Shitheads!
我们走吧 - 妈的
- Let's go. - Fuck!
案子这边有新情况发生
We've got a situation going on...
- 妈的
Shit!
梅利曼 你在干什么呢？
What the fuck are you doing, Merrimen?
说吧
Yeah?
我们是警察 请别挂断电话
This is the Police Department. Please don't hang up.
我叫丹尼
My name's Danny,
只有负责与你联系 除了我没人会打电话给你
I'll be your only contact. Nobody else is going to call you.
你是劫匪头领吗？
Is this the person in charge?
我是分行经理
This is the branch manager.
代表劫匪头领跟你说话
I'm speaking on the man in charge's behalf.
分行经理 你叫什么？
Do you have a name, branch manager?
听着 他们已经杀死了一名人质 是个女的
Listen. They've already killed one of the hostages. A woman.
他们不会跟你联络
They will not speak to you again.
如果在他们的要求未满足前 你再打电话来 他们还会杀死一名人质的
If you call back again before their demands are met, they'll kill another.
赶紧把他们要的东西给他们吧
Just send what they want.
钱和直升机在准备了
The money and the chopper are en route,
都需要时间来安排
but it's going to take a little bit of time.
我需要至少90分钟 可以么
You need to give me at least 90 minutes. Is this doable?
可以 别再打电话了
Okay. Don't call back.
这个区域是哪里
What's the prefix here?
长滩 562区
562. It's Long Beach.
你好
Hello?
你在看吗？
You watching?
是的
Yup.
你准备如何脱身呢？
So how the hell are you going to get out of this one?
我还没想好呢
Not sure yet.
你从那个脱衣女郎那要到的我的电话号？
Did you get my number from her cell?
休想让我戴上手铐
I ain't cuffing up.
无所谓
That's okay.
反正我今天没带手铐
I didn't bring my cuffs anyway.
这我猜到了
Yeah, I can see that.
是他吗？
Was that who I think it was?
- 是的
Yup.
直升机到位时
We've got a chopper that's gonna come down.
会在这里降落
The chopper is going to land right over here.
正面有几个入口可以突进去 正门入口是行不通了
I've got two-door entry on one. One-door entry on two.
炸弹安好了
Breaching!
他们把金库大门炸开了
Well, they just blew the vault.
发生什么了？
What the fuck?
这里是美联储 您是哪里?
Federal Reserve, accounts receiving.
我这里是阿拉米达
Hey, it's Al at Alameda.
从皮科里维拉银行要运过来一批钱
We have a drop at Pico Rivera we need to schedule.
您看安排周三下午两点接受如何？
How's Wednesday at 2:00?
可以的 安排在18号下午两点 是吗？
That works. You're confirmed for 2:00 p.m. the 18th.
是的 非常感谢
Great. Thanks.
我们在这 对吧？ - 是的
- We're here, yeah? - Yeah, that's us.
这是什么？
So what is this?
是污水管道
This is the sewer line,
如果图纸没错的话 这都是水泥管道
and according to this map right here, it's all cemented up.
直升机申请进行到哪一步了？
Hey, where are we with the chopper?
还在等审批
We're waiting on clearance.
别担心 反正他们也跑不了
Relax, they're not going anywhere.
还等个毛审批 我们必须行动了
To hell with clearance. We've got to move.
奥布莱恩
O'Brien, hey!
他是不是出门忘吃药了？
Is he off his meds?
跟他说让他赶紧滚回来
Tell him to get the fuck back here!
闭嘴行么
Will you shut the fuck up?
去你妈的
Oh, fuck you.
我们得去支援他
We better go back him up.
尼克奔正门去了 我们得去支援
Nick's heading to the front. We're on the move.
行动
Here we go.
我了个去 他是认真的吗？
- Fuck! - Is he serious?
大家都还好吗？
Everybody okay?
是的
Yes.
求求你 老天 救救我吧 我想再见到家人
Please, Lord, please, let me see my family again.
尼克你在哪？ - 洛杉矶县治安官
- Nick! - Sheriff's Department.
尼克？
Nick!
这里安全
Clear!
我这也安全
- 他妈的 - 尼克 你在哪？
- The fuck? - Nick, what's your location?
你在哪？
What's your location?
你好 还是阿拉米达给您致电 我不记得
Hey, this is Al at Alameda again.
达皮科里维拉银行出库的时间了
I forgot to schedule a drop at the Pico Rivera Savings.
你们今天安排的是几点来着？
What do you have open today?
"黑猫" 我是"白猫" 时间确认了吗？
Ghetto Bird, this is Silverback. We confirmed?
确认了 是两点四十五 也就是两分钟之后
Check. Appointment's at 2:45. That's in two minutes.
运往皮科里维拉银行
Pico Rivera.
"马力" 一切都准备就绪了吗？
Horsepower all set?
是的 都准备妥当了
Yeah, I'm ready to go.
你们是新来的？
They got you on a new route?
是啊 这周刚给我们调过来
Yeah. Yeah, they just switched us over this week.
好的 给我看看你们的证件
All right. Let me get you guys' IDs, man.
好的 给你
Yeah, sure. There you go.
好了
All right.
你们可以过去了
You're good to go.
- 谢谢 - 打开大门 - 过去吧
- All right, thank you. - Open the gate. Have a good one.
该死
Oh, fuck.
皮科里维拉银行2.2？
Pico Rivera Savings? 2.2?
是的 是我们
Yup, that's us.
把钱车推上来吧
Bring her up.
准备 1 2 3拉
All right, ready. One, two, three.
在这签字 - 好的
- Sign here. - You got it.
马克 你是新来的？
You're new here, Mark?
是的
Yes, sir.
你们来的有点晚啊
You guys running a little bit late.
是的 我们来的时候有点堵
Yeah, we ran into some traffic, so...
我不知道你俩以前在哪运钞
I don't know where they had you guys routed before,
但是在我们这 交接时间是非常严格的
but we run a tight, tight ship around here,
如果你们要迟到了的话 必须先打电话通知这里一声
so, if you're going to be late, have base call it in.
没问题 这次是我工作有失
Yeah, no problem. That's my fault. I just...
记住下次打电话
Just have them call.
跟我来吧
On me.
嘿 路易吉 阿拉米达那批钱运到了 你去接受吧
Hey, Luigi. Alameda's on deck. Check them in.
收到
Copy that.
是新人
New guys.
我出去看看
I'm going to step out for a minute.
哥几个你们好啊
How you guys doing today?
- 你好
- Good. All right. - Good.
嘿 你好吗？
How you doing?
- 还不错 你呢 - 我也很好 谢谢
- All right, how are you? - Good, thank you.
请在这里签字
Sign that for me, please.
都是百元面值的吗？
All hundreds?
- 第一车里的都是百元面值的 第二车什么面值的都有
The first one's all hundreds. The second one is mixed.
我们这边有点忙不过来
We're a little backed up.
- 好的 尽快就行
All right, do what you can.
- 你们先等等 喝杯饮料什么的吧 非常感谢
Guys want to hang out, get a Coke or something? Appreciate you.
- 谢谢
Thank you.
我们需要方圆250米地下管道检查权限
We're going to need access to the recording off-site.
能搞定么
Can you get that to us?
- 了解 你需要看心理专家
- Understood. - You need professional help.
说得对
Desperately.
刚才是我不对 这现场交给你了
My bad last time. Your crime scene.
"白猫" 我是"马力" 我已就位
Silverback, this is Horsepower. I'm in.
"绿猫" 我是"白猫" "马力"已就位
Greenpeace, this is Silverback. Horsepower is in.
收到 "白猫" 现在关灯
Roger that, Silverback. Lights out.
好吧 我们去看看
Okay, here we go.
强尼 又他妈断电
Johnny, we're fucking brown again, man.
停止一切工作 让他们离开点钞室
Got to shut down. Pull them out of the count rooms.
停电了
We're going brown.
我们要关闭一会儿 所有人去休息吧
We've got to shut down for a bit. All teams go ahead and take 10.
路易吉 出来吧
Luigi, come on.
好的
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
根据断电应对程序 他们都出来了
They went to brown. They're clearing out.
我们去把门都锁好 - 好的
- Let's lock it down. - Copy.
准备行动
Get ready to go.
启动电磁脉冲
Powering up EMP now.
全部检查完毕
All clear here.
可以行动了
Good to go.
外面安全了 你出来吧
You're clear. Go.
好像这出了点问题
Shit. Check something out.
你觉得是哪里坏了？
What do you think it is?
百元面值钞票计数室的摄像头坏了吗？
Are the cameras up in the 100 room?
坏了
Uh, negative.
555-01-43.
555-0143.
他们太慢啦
It's taking too long.
这里是订餐热线
Tasty Orders.
我是美联储的莎伦
This is Sharon at the Fed.
我一个半小时前定的餐
Now, we ordered almost an hour and a half ago.
我们午休都要过了怎么还没送来？
Now, I only have so much time on my lunch break.
在路上了 马上就送到
It coming! Be there in a few minute!
他们刚打电话给中餐馆
They just called for the Chinese.
动作快点
Hurry it up.
动作感应警报也失灵了吗？
Motion is out in there, too.
是啊 供电还没恢复呢
Yeah, man, we're still brown.
我们得重写程序 赶紧启动
You know, we better override. Power it up.
是啊
All right.
搞定了
Done.
让他们重新数一遍钱
Okay. Better get that count, too.
糟糕 警卫过来了 快藏好
Shit, here comes security. Get down. Get down.
我们得检查一下百元面值钞票计数室 动作感应警报失灵了
Hey, man, we got to check this 100 count. Motion went off.
路易吉你听到了吗？
Luigi...
快按住对讲键 让他们不能说话
Step on it. Step on it, quick.
怎么了？
Yeah?
- 路易吉 - 该死
- Luigi. - Yeah?
路易吉 你占着线呢兄弟
Damn, dude! Luigi, you're stepping on the line, man!
拉塞尔你说什么
Say again? Russell?
嘿 笨蛋 你得松开按键才能说话
Hey, dumb-dumb. You've got to let go of the push to talk.
收到 我去找他
What the hell is going on here today?
路易吉一直联系不上
Luigi, man. He's stepping all over the line.
这家伙手忙脚乱的
He's hot-micing like a motherfucker.
他在食堂呢 去找他吧
He's in the cafeteria. Go ahead and get him.
好的 收到 我过去看看
All right. Roger that. I'm stepping out.
你安全了 快动手
You're clear. Go.
老天爷啊
Holy shit.
路易吉 你一直不松开对讲键呢
Luigi, you're hot-micing.
你得松开按键才能说话
You've got to let go of the talk button. You're stepping on the line.
嘿 我没一直按着对讲键
Dude, it's not me.
我们得重新数一遍百元钞票 叫上你的搭档
Come on, we've got to check the 100 count. Let's go. Get Junior. Let's go.
转到五号线了
Switch to line five.
你还有不到2分钟的时间了 速度快点
You got about a minute and a half, two minutes. Let's go.
他们回来了 赶紧撤退
They're back. Get out.
路易吉 你看到什么了吗？
Luigi, you see anything, man?
什么也没看到
Yeah, we're good. There's nothing back there but dust.
你让我来看什么？
What am I looking for?
没事 我要找点乐子 你再数一遍钱
Don't worry about it, man. I'm gonna juice up the room. Run the count,
- 确保没有任何问题 好吗？ - 收到
- and make sure we're good, all right? - Copy that.
你在哪？
Where are you?
我是"马力" 我在排气管道里呢
This is Horsepower. I'm in the vents.
"绿猫" 你那边任务结束了 撤吧
Greenpeace, you're done. Cut out.
电力恢复了
We are back up, brother.
全体注意 回到钞票计数室
All teams, back to the count room.
通知洛杉矶警局中心
Get on with LAPD Central.
我们在第八和格兰大道上 跟踪监视嫌犯
Tell them we're running surveillance at 8th and Grand.
代码5 不要惊动嫌犯
Request a Code 5. We do not wanna spook the suspects.
收到 代码5已生效
Copy that. Putting in a Code 5.
是我记错了吗 我怎么记得这里原来是装满钱的？
Am I tripping or was this full before?
我们再说一遍吧
Let's just check the count.
是712200美元吗？
$712,200.
是的
拉塞尔 钱数没错
Russell, the count is on.
好的 收到
All right, roger that. Go ahead and clock out Alameda.
把结果通知阿拉米达吧
Take Alameda out.
钱数没错
The count was good.
但你两个钱箱都是半满的
But both of your bins were half-full.
你说什么？
Sorry?
你两个钱箱都是半满的
Your bins, they were half-full.
给我的时候就是这样
That's how we got them.
下次来时 这点钱装袋子里就行
Next time, just put it in a cash sack.
不用这么麻烦的
Makes things a lot easier.
用脑子工作 别蛮干
Try and work smart, not hard.
好主意 谢谢
Okay, sounds good. Thanks for the advice.
我们本来想给你小费的 但是你来得太晚了
We would tip you, honey, but that just took too damn long, okay?
我们饭店只有我一个送餐的 抱歉了
I'm the only guy they've got delivering today. I'm sorry.
抱歉 哥们 我还得看一下你们的运钞文件
Sorry, guys, let me see your drop confirmation again.
- 好的 - 给你
- All right. - There you go.
中餐餐馆的？
Chinese food guy?
让他进去
Go on. Buzz him in.
让他在那等着
Hold him there.
2:45
2-4-5.
让他过来
Yeah, send him through.
过来一下 小伙
Come here for a sec, buddy.
我没看到你进来时的签名呢
Yeah, man, I don't have you signed in.
你叫什么？
Where's your name?
我签字了啊 你上一班的人看着我签的
Come on, man, I signed my name with a dude from the last shift, man.
我不知道怎么跟你说
I don't know what to tell you.
这饭菜可真"好吃"啊
Damn you finicky.
我得让他们退我钱 - 对
- I'm getting my money back. - Okay.
确认完了
That's all I need.
好了 你们可以走了
All right, you boys are good to go.
非常感谢 - 放松些
- Thank you very much, Officer. - Take it easy.
- 祝你今天愉快 - 好的
- You have a good day. - All right.
行吧 你走吧 - 再见
- Go on. Get out of here. - Thank you.
请帮我接大厅警卫
Yes, security in the lobby, please.
这里是大厅警卫
Lobby.
- 你看到那个送餐的了吗
Yeah, did you see a delivery guy?
他是个浅肤色黑人 穿着红色上衣 差不多一米八高
Red shirt, light skin. About 6 foot.
怎么了？ - 别让他走
- Wait, what? - Stop him.
你们负责左侧 我们负责右侧
You got eyes on the 1-2 side? We'll cover the 3-4 corner.
收到
Copy that.
我刚在警卫岗耽搁了一下 你在哪？
Got held up at security. What's your location?
- 在格兰南大街 刚过弗农大道
South on Grand, just past Vernon.
右转上了盖奇大道 右转上了盖奇大道
Go right on Gage. Right on Gage.
- 收到
Copy that.
下车 速度快点
Move! Let's go! Get out!
- 下车 速度快点 - 别激动
- Come on, move! Move! Here we go! - It's cool.
快下来 - 别激动
- Come on, get down! Go! Go! Go! - It's cool. I'm cool, man.
别激动
Be cool, bro. Cool.
操
Fuck.
他在那 红衣服的那个 往前开两个路口
There he is. There he is. Red shirt. Two blocks ahead.
发现嫌犯
Eyes on suspect.
他正向9点钟方向奔希尔大街去了
Walking eastbound on 9th, approaching Hill, south side of street.
在前面截住他
Pull up in front of him, in front of him.
抓住这个王八蛋
Let's get this motherfucker.
先把他抓到车里吧
Let's ram his bitch-ass into the gate first.
他妈的上车 滚上车
Get in the fucking car! Come on. Get in.
他妈的
Fuck.
揍他
Hit him!
妈的 别乱动
Motherfucker.
速度点 尽快完事好撤退
All right, let's go. Let's go. Let's get it done as quick as we can.
你他妈的
Little fuck.
那个混蛋在哪？
Where is he? Where the fuck is he, asshole?
混蛋
Fuck.
把耳机给我拿下来 那混蛋在哪？
Fucking... Fucker!
把一次性电话交出来 他在哪
Give me the burner phone. Where the fuck is he?
太平洋地平线垃圾站
Pacific Horizon Salvage.
南门 他们在那集合
In South Gate. That's the rally point.
我是"白猫" 说吧
Silverback, go.
"马力"被抓了
Horsepower's burned.
再说一遍 我听不清
Repeat that. I can't hear you.
"马力"被抓了
Horsepower is burned.
他废了
He's done.
我现在还安全 我去哪跟你们汇合？
I'm still clean. Where am I going, bro?
该死
Fuck!
速度快点 钱你们都收好了吗？
Let's go. Let's go. You guys got it all?
- 是的 都在这了 - 好的 都带走
- Yes, it's all in. - Pick it up.
- 好的
It's good.
太平洋地平线垃圾站 在阿拉米达支路附近
Pacific Horizon Salvage. South Gate, Alameda Corridor.
我马上到
10-4. Headed to you.
其他人怎么样？了
What happened to the other two?
都被抓了
They got burned.
发现嫌犯
Eyes on suspects.
黑色四门雪佛兰巨无霸
Black, four-door Suburban!
我们正沿着哈罗大道向南开
Heading southbound on Alameda.
马上到劳森大道了 你们在圣达非跟我汇合
Approaching Slauson Avenue. I need you to parallel me on Santa Fe.
前面堵车了 怎么回事？
We got some traffic up ahead. What's going on?
路堵死了
Corridor's backed up.
我们刚从阿拉米达支路出来 正往南开
We just turned down Alameda Corridor, heading south.
该死
Shit.
正在接近嫌犯 嫌犯在6点钟方向
Coming up on suspect, six o'clock.
- 真堵
Shit.
右翼队伍正在接近
Right lane is closed up ahead.
我重复 右翼队伍正在接近
I repeat, right lane is closed up ahead.
看到了吗？
You guys see that?
20 30辆车后面的那车是警察吗?
Twenty, 30 cars back. What is that?
是警察吗？
Is that...
好了 停车
Okay, we're at a stop, stop, stop.
等不了支援部队了 我们得行动了
Fuck backup. We've got to move now.
该死
Fuck.
是的
Yup.
是警察
That's them.
给我防弹衣
- Give me my vest. - Yeah.
- 好的 给你
Yeah, here we go.
他们堵在那了 我们得在交通顺畅之前抓住他们
Okay, we've got them pinched in. We've got to move before it opens up.
给他戴上手铐
Cuff him up.
注意 嫌犯有防弹衣
Be advised, suspects wearing body armor.
不要瞄准躯干射击 瞄准四肢和头部射击
No center mass shots. Limb and head shots only.
收到 往那边开
Copy that. Go around right here.
都卡住了
It's jammed up.
准备好了么 出发
Good? Okay, let's go.
该死 - 怎么了？
- Oh, shit. - What?
- 他们从车里出来了
They're getting out of the car.
Z 去右翼包抄
Z, go down the right.
格斯 博拉科跟我走中路
Gus, Borracho, center with me.
默夫 你在左翼 别往上冲
Murph, stay on the left. Don't come in.
把自动步枪给我
- Pass me the saw. - Fuck.
我们上
Let's go.
趴下
Stay down. Stay down.
Get down. Get down.
县治安官 趴下 - 趴下
- Sheriff's Department. Stay down. - Get down. Get down.
县治安官 趴下
- Get down. - Sheriff's Department, stay down.
趴下 躲在发动机后面
Get down. Get down. Stay by the engine block.
趴下 躲到方向盘后面去
Get down behind the wheel.
县治安官 女士 回到车里去
Sheriff's Department. Lady, get in the car.
该死
Oh, shit.
博拉科
Borracho!
换位置
Moving!
Moving.
格斯和默夫 你们穿过去截住他们 可以吧？
Gus, Murph, you two go across and cut them off, okay?
托尼·Z 准备好了吗？
Tony Z, you ready?
上
Let's go.
换位置
Moving!
换弹夹
Move!
换位置
Moving. Moving.
换弹夹
Mag change!
换位置
Moving.
换弹夹
Mag change.
快走
Moving!
Go! Go!
托尼 你怎么样？
Tony, you okay?
- 上 上 - 你没事吧
- Yeah, go! Go! - You okay?
该死
Fuck!
快跑
Go!
掩护他
Cover!
快跑
Move.
该死
Fuck!
他在砖墙那边
Brick wall! Brick wall!
他跑到砖砌建筑物后面去了
Behind the brick building!
我的孩子
My kids...
你跑不掉了
You're in His hands now.
听懂了吗？
You hear me?
该死
Fuck!
别逼我
Don't do it.
早跟你说过了吧
Told you.
是啊 你说过
Yeah. You did.
什么鬼
What the fuck?
你看这个
You see this?
帮我都打开
Here. Do those.
该死
Oh, shit.
他们弄这东西做什么 雪景球吗？
So what? They were going to make fucking snow globes?
做一万个？
Like 10,000 of them?
去看队员们怎么样了没？
You check on the boys?
我会去医院看一眼他们
Yeah, I'm going to roll to the hospital.
你要给博拉科的妻子打个电话吗？
You gonna call Borracho's wife?
打啊
Yeah.
好的
All right.
他们本计划去海港的
This won't go to Harbor.
你失去了一个伙伴 我深表遗憾
I'm sorry you lost one of your guys.
谢谢
Thanks.
你还好吗？
You all right?
我还好
Yeah, I'm okay.
我没事
Yeah.
尼克 你得戒烟了
Nick, you've got to stop smoking, man.
试试这个
Here.
有机的哦
It's organic.
这些都会归功给联邦调查局 你知道的吧？
You know everything was accounted for at the Fed, right?
当然知道
Apparently so.
唐尼在吗？
Hey, is Donnie around?
他辞职了
He quit.
你在附近有再见到他吗？
So you haven't seen him anywhere?
我说了 他辞职了
I said he quit.
两天前辞的
Two days ago.
要来瓶啤酒吗？
You want a beer?
给我来一瓶吧
Very much so. Like 50.
谢谢 不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
你看到单位新来的小妞了么？
Did you see that new chick? Little fat-ass?
就是臀部很性感的那个？
The new girl who works down the hall?
哥几个最近怎么样？
What's going on, gentlemen?
哥们 - 你还 - 真高兴你能来
- Gentlemen, good to see you. - Yo!
- 你好吗？ - 你妻子知道你来这里吗？
- Good to see you. - Your wife know where you are?
你是怎么拿到这份工作的
How did you get that job?
你真的会数数么
Can you actually count?
我能控制整个环境
I'm in complete control of my environment.
没人能知道我怎么做到的
People don't even know.
他妈的小妞
Fucking Fräulein.
各位兄弟
What's going on, boys?
还好吗？ 都还不错嘛？
How you doing? You good?
要喝点啤酒吗？
Some beers?
嘿 服务员
Hey, guv.
给我这些哥们上酒
A round of beers for my mates.
你想喝什么？
And for you?
我要求不高
I'm easy.
想不到喝什么
I don't know.
你帮我选个好的吧
Surprise me.
好的
I can do that.
干杯 - 干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
你为什么找我？
So why you come to me?
你很凶悍
You're a beast, man.
而且除了你也没人能干成这事
Plus, you're the only one that can pull this off.
听着
Listen.
如果我答应干着票的话 就得我说了算
We do this, I call the shots.
得用我的人 这票算是我的 不是你的
My crew, my job, not yours.
懂了么？
Got it?
我懂 - 就得这么来
- Completely understand. - That's the way it has to be.
就这些
That's it.
这都是我的宝贝
It's my baby.
我就弄到这些
That's what I've got.
你怎么弄到这些的？
How did you get a hold of all this stuff?
你在酒吧就能弄到这些东西？
You got this all at that bar?
我费了很多时间才收集到这些的
Collected it over time.
哇哦
Wow.
这是超人才能干的活
Job for Superman.
干杯
Cheers.
谢谢 我很喜欢别人叫我公主
Thank you. I love when you call me Princess.
你在街对面上班吗？
You work across the street?
- 是啊
Yeah.
在钻石交易所？
Diamond exchange?
- 是啊
That's right.
这酒算我请你的
Beer's on me.